Jimmy Han

jimzy@outlook.com (818) 532-8969

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY / NETWORK SPECIALIST

Administration · Optimization · Design · Troubleshooting · Implementation

SUMMARY:

A highly motivated professional with over 10 years' experience in technical/desktop support and 4 years experience in network administration. Proficient in installing, configuring and upgrading Microsoft suite of applications both on server and client. A team player with strong analytical and problem solving skills as well as possessing excellent customer service skills. Excellent interpersonal and communication skills and work well with clients and all levels of management and staff.

EDUCATION:

Computer Education Institute - Microsoft Computer Systems Engineer

CERTIFICATIONS:

MCP - Microsoft Certified Professional CNA - Novell Certified A+ Certified Dell Certified Technician

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

MS Server Administration in Office and Data Center environment, Active Directory, DHCP, DNS, DFS, WDS, SCOM, SSL VPN, WSUS, IIS, FTP, ColdFusion Admin, Bit Defender Management, Barracuda Spam Firewall, Hyper V 2008, Imail Server Administration, SolarWinds, Foundry Networks Load Balance, Netscreen Firewall, and Imaging.

EXPERIENCE:

uSamp

Corp System Administrator/Helpdesk

4/2012 - 9/2016

Provide helpdesk support for about 200 users between 5 offices within the U.S., London and India. Responsible for managing file server backups, active directory, email services, office VOIP phones, corporate conference lines, network printers, software licensing, IT equipment purchasing, asset management and any other technical related tasks to keep company running.

11/2009 -3/2012

<u>Intuit – Contractor</u> Desktop Support

Assist end users with the installation, configuration and ongoing usability of desktop/laptop computers, peripheral equipment and software. Ensure desktop computers interconnect seamlessly with diverse systems including associated validation systems, file servers, email servers, computer

conferencing systems, application servers and administrative systems.

<u>Combined LA Westside Multiple Listing Service</u> Network Administrator

3/2005 - 5/2009

Install and configure servers for development, staging and production environments. Monitor and manage network, database and web servers. DHCP, DNS, Active Directory and GPO management. End user desktop support. Server backups, e-mail server management for appox. 15,000 users, barracuda spam firewall, monitor and maintain data center, approx 50 servers. Implement and deploy new technology. Asset management, work directly with vendors for software/hardware service contracts. Migrated existing MS Virtual 2005 nodes and migrated over to Hyper V 2008 server. Deployed, managed, and monitored, configured resource priority on new virtual machines as needed. SCOM used for monitoring server resource and analyzing usage, aslo configured for server alerts to the technical staff.

<u>Tek Systems,</u> Thousand Oaks, CA Technical Support / Management Level 1/2004 - 02/2005

Contracted by Verizon, working as a technical support specialist in a call center environment and provide customer service support to our business DSL customers, duties on a daily basis, troubleshoot browsing issues, internet connectivity, slow speeds, monitor switch traffic, analyze provisioning, order issues, trouble ticket documentation via remedy, assist customers with setup, remote desktop access, and maintain good customer relations.

E-Systems Design, Brea, CA 05/2000 – 11/2003 Systems Analyst / Technical Support Specialist

Employed by PC Systems, contracted by Boeing. Image PC's with O/S and configure for network and mail. Migrate users to Windows 2000-XP. Respond to service calls for desktop support. Install software and hardware, repair Dell laptops, and also responsible for data transfers over the network for existing users. Troubleshoot printer connections and network connectivity in a LAN environment of over 6,000 users. Migration emails from Exchange to Outlook.

Moraga Investments, Los Angeles, CA

01/2000 - 04/2000

Technical Support Specialist

Install and configure O/S and software applications on both desktop and laptop. Troubleshoot network connectivity, and troubleshoot printer issues in a LAN environment. Support end user for both software and hardware issues.